My achievements and conquests will be evaluated in the future
Tesla is a history, drama film directed by Michael Almereyda.
The story of the Promethean struggles of Nikola Tesla, as he attempts to transcend entrenched
technology—including his own previous work—by pioneering a system of wireless energy that would change the world.
Nikola Tesla, played by Ethan Hawke.
Anne Morgan, played by Eve Hewson.
George Westinghouse, played by Jim Gaffigan.
Thomas Edison, played by Kyle MacLachlan.
J.P. Morgan, played by Donnie Keshawarz.
Robert Underwood Johnson, played by Josh Hamilton.
Tesla is a 2020 American biographical drama film
written and directed by Michael Almereyda.
It stars Ethan Hawke as Nikola Tesla.
Eve Hewson, Ebon Moss-Bachrach, Jim Gaffigan, and Kyle MacLachlan also star.
The film had its world premiere at the 2020 Sundance Film Festival on January 27, 2020, and was
released in selected theaters and via Premium VOD on August 21, 2020, by IFC Films.
The film explores themes of inventor, biography, based
on true story, nikola tesla, tesla coil.
The tone is emotional.